Guide to the CASA Latina Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
CASA Latina records
1950-2020
1989-2015
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5975
5975-001
CASA Latina
13.8 cubic feet (13 boxes) plus 141 MB (1,162 digital files)
Records related to the history and operation of CASA Latina, a worker center and nonprofit organization based in Seattle, Washington. [Registros relacionados a la historia y modo de operación de CASA Latina, un centro de trabajadores y organización sin fin de lucros basada en Seattle, Washington]
CASA Latina is a worker center and Seattle-based nonprofit that works to educate, assist and empower Latinx and immigrant workers. Founded in 1994 to address the needs of a growing number of Latinx workers arriving in Seattle, the organization began by doing street outreach in borrowed spaces, becoming a nonprofit in 1995. Since 2009, CASA Latina runs a labor dispatch hall and training programs out of a custom-designed, three-building campus in Seattle’s Central District. The campus provides a home for CASA Latina’s ESL classes, job skills and safety training workshops, as well as community organizing for over 750 worker-members.
The "CASA" in CASA Latina stands for Centro de Ayuda Solidaria a los Amigos, which means "Center for Help in Solidarity with Friends." CASA Latina made history in 2014 when it affiliated with the Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, becoming the first worker center to join the executive board of the state AFL-CIO body. CASA Latina had earlier affiliated with the WSLC in 2009. CASA Latina joined forces with the Martin Luther King County Labor Council in Seattle in 2014. Nationally, CASA Latina is affiliated with the National Day Laborer Organizing Network and National Domestic Workers Alliance. CASA Latina’s programs, curricula, and operations have served as a model for worker centers throughout the country.
[CASA Latina es un centro de trabajadores y una organización sin fines de lucro basada en Seattle que existe para educar, asistir y apoderar a trabajadores Latinx e inmigrantes. Fundado en 1994 para responder a las necesidades de un gran número de trabajadores Latinx llegando a Seattle, la organización empezó por alcance callejero en lugares prestados y se convirtió en una organización sin fines de lucro en 1995. Desde 2009, CASA Latina maneja un centro de trabajo y programas de entrenamiento en un campus de tres edificios, de diseño personalizado, localizado en el Central District en Seattle. En este campus, CASA Latina provee clases de inglés, talleres de habilidades y seguridad en el trabajo, y organización comunitaria para 750 miembros-trabajadores.
La “CASA” en CASA Latina significa Centro de Ayuda Solidaria a los Amigos. CASA Latina hizo historia en 2014 cuando se junt al Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, haciéndose el primer centro de trabajadores de ser parte de la junta ejecutiva del cuerpo AFL-CIO del estado. CASA Latina se había afiliado con el WSLC en 2009. CASA Latina se junto al Martin Luther King County Labor Council en Seattle en 2014. Al nivel nacional casa latina está afiliado al National Day Laborer Organizing Network (red nacional de organizar jornaleros) y National Domestic Workers Alliance (alianza nacional de trabajadores domésticos). Los programas, el currículo y las operaciones de CASA Latina han servido como modelo para centros de trabajadores al través del país.]
The collection has been arranged into the following series and subseries [Esta collección fue organizada en series y subseries como]:
SERIES 1: HISTORICAL AND ORGANIZATIONAL MATERIALS [SERIE 1: MATERIALES HISTÓRICOS Y ORGANIZATIVOS], 1950,1989-2009
Subseries A: CASA Latina History [Subserie A: Historia de CASA Latina], 1950, 1989-2006
Subseries B: Organizational Process and Charts [Subserie B: Organigramas y Proceso de Organización], 2000-2009
Subseries C: Bylaws [Subserie C: Estatutos], 1995-2006
Subseries D: Employee Handbooks and Training [Subserie D: Manuales y Entrenamiento para Empleos], 2001-2008
SERIES 2: EXECUTIVE BOARD [SERIE 2: JUNTA DIRECTIVA], 1996-2015
Subseries A: Board History and Composition [Subserie A: Historia y Composición de la Junta Directiva], 1997-2005
Subseries B: Board Training and Orientation Materials [Subserie B: Materiales de Orientación y Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva], 1996-2003
Subseries C: Meeting Minutes and Attached Materials [Subserie C: Notas y Documentos de la Junta Directiva], 1995-2015
SERIES 3: REPORTS AND STATISTICS [SERIE 3: REPORTES Y ESTADÍSTICAS], 1995-2009
Subseries A: Work and Business Plans [Subserie A: Planes para Trabajos y Negocios], 1996-2006
Subseries B: Annual Reports [Subserie B: Reportes Anuales], 1995-2005
Subseries C: Program and Outcomes Data [Subserie C: Datos sobre Programas y Resultados], 1996-2009
SERIES 4: GENERAL OFFICE FILES [SERIE 4: ARCHIVOS GENERALES DE OFICINA], 1994-2009
Subseries A: Correspondence [Subserie A: Correspondencia], 1999-2007
Subseries B: Financial Records [Subserie B: Registros Financieros], 1994-2009
Subseries C: Staff Meetings [Subserie C: Notas de la Reunión de Personal], 1994-2002
SERIES 5: PROGRAM FILES [SERIE 5: ARCHIVOS DE PROGRAMAS], 1992-2014
Subseries A: Education and Literacy Programs [Subserie A: Programas de Educación y Literacia], 1992-2008
Subseries B: English as a Second Language (ESL) [Subserie B: Inglés como Segundo Idioma (ESL)], 1991-1998
Subseries C: Worker Education and Organizing [Subserie C: Educación y Organización de Trabajadores], 1994-2014
Subseries D: Immigrant Rights [Subserie D: Derechos de Inmigrantes], 1997-2009
Subseries E: Legislative Advocacy and Lobbying [Subserie E: Cabildeo y Defensa Legislativa], 1997-2009
Subseries F: Capacity Building Programs [Subserie F: Programas para Crecer Capacidad], 1993-2009
SERIES 6: CONTRACTS AND AGREEMENTS [SERIE 6: CONTRATOS Y ACUERDOS], 1993-2010
SERIES 7: WORKER CENTER BUILDING RECORDS [SERIE 7: ARCHIVOS DE FACILIDAD CENTRO DE TRABAJADORES], 1996-2010
SERIES 8: PUBLICITY, NEWSLETTERS, AND BROCHURES [SERIE 8: PUBLICIDAD, BOLETINES Y FOLLETOS], 1993-2015
Subseries A: Speeches, Advertising, and Publications [Subserie A: Discursos, Publicidad y Publicaciones], 1993-2013
Subseries B: Newsletters and Brochures [Subserie B: Boletines y Folletos], 1996-2015
Subseries C: Photographs and Video [Subserie C: Fotografías y Video], 1997-2008
SERIES 9: ORGANIZATION SUBJECT FILES [SERIE 9: ARCHIVOS POR TEMA DE ORGANIZACIONES], 1993-2009
SERIES 10: CASA LATINA WEBSITE [SERIE 10: SITIO WEB DE CASA LATINA], 2013-2020
This collection contains the records of CASA Latina, including the office files of Hilary Stern, founding Executive Director of CASA Latina from 1994-2016. The majority of the organizational records relate to the history, governance, founding, funding, finances, operations, and programs of CASA Latina, including legislative lobbying and advocacy records. The collection also contains records of the Executive Board, including paper-based and digital meeting materials, records of decisions, and Executive Director reports. Promotional materials include newsletters, flyers, press releases, and speech materials created by or about CASA Latina. The collection also contains digital captures of the CASA Latina website beginning in 2013.
Also included are CASA Latina building plans for its current three-building campus in the Central District, reflecting a community-centered process for the design of the space itself, efforts to foster connections with area residents, and building and construction plans.
[Esta colección contiene registros de CASA Latina incluyendo documentos de la oficina de Hilary Stern, Directora Ejecutiva fundadora de CASA Latina desde 1994 hasta 2016. La mayoría de los registros organizativos son relacionados a la historia, gobernancia, fundación, finanzas, operaciones, y programas de CASA Latina, incluyendo registros sobre trabajo de cabildeo. La colección también contiene registros físicos y digitales de la junta ejecutiva incluyendo materiales de juntas, registros de decisiones y reportes de la directora ejecutiva. Estaría los promocionales incluso boletines, volantes, comunicados de prensa, y materiales de discursos hechos por o sobre CASA Latina.
También incluido son planes de construcción para el campus actual de tres edificios de CASA Latina, en el área Central District. Los registros reflejan un proceso de diseño enfocado en conectar con residentes del área, en proveer para las necesidades de la comunidad del lugar, y los planes de construcción.]
Forms part of the Labor Archives of Washington
Open to all users. [Restricciónes de Acceso: Abierto para todos los usuarios].
No user access copy is currently available for digital files. Arrangements can be made to preview the digital materials onsite in the Special Collections Reading Room by contacting Special Collections well in advance of your visit.
CASA Latina, Hilary Stern, 2016-01-20. [Información De Adquisición: Donadores: CASA Latina, Hilary Stern, 2016-01-20.]
The CASA Latina web site has been regularly crawled by Archive-It since 2013. The snapshots can be viewed online via the UW Libraries Archive-It database.
SeaTac Seattle Minimum Wage History Project records. Accession No. 6025-001
CASA Latina$vArchives; CASA Latina$xFinance; CASA Latina$xAdministration; United Way of America$xResearch grants$vSources; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Literacy*AmeriCorps; Nonprofit organizations$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Immigrants$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Immigrants$zWashington (State)$zSeattle$xSocial conditions; Foreign workers$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Social work with immigrants$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Press releases; By-laws; Ephemera; Minutes (Records); Annual reports; Records (Documents); Newsletters; Stern, Hilary; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Latinos and Latinas
- HISTORICAL AND ORGANIZATIONAL MATERIALS [SERIE 1: MATERIALES HISTÓRICOS Y ORGANIZATIVOS], 1950, 1989-2009; 1989-2009; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/13, 1/91, 2/33, 3/3, 3/7, 3/10, 3/78, 3/82, 4/4, 4/5, 4/17, 4/19, 4/20, 4/21, 4/43, 7/13, 7/48, 8/18, 8/19, 8/60, 9/19, 9/48, 10/15-20, 11/39)
  History, bylaws, organizational charts, and employee handbooks and manuals, some of which are written or translated into Spanish. Related history materials intended for publicity can be found in SERIES 8: PUBLICITY, NEWSLETTERS AND BROCHURES.
  [Historia, estatutos, organigramas, y manuales para empleos, unos escritos o traducidos en Español. Materiales relacionados destinados para publicidad se encuentran en SERIE 8: PUBLICIDAD, BOLETINES Y FOLLETOS]
  - CASA Latina History [Subserie A: Historia de CASA Latina], 1950, 1989-2006; Subseries A (Box-folder 3/3, 3/82, 4/4, 4/5, 4/17, 4/19, 4/20, 7/48, 8/18, 8/19, 8/60)
    - Meeting Notes and Other Examples of CASA Latina [Notas de Juntas y Otros Ejemplos de CASA Latina], 2002 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Introduction of CASA Latina [Introducción a CASA Latina] (Box-folder 3/82)
    - Community Support Packet of CASA Latina (History) [Paquete de Soporte Comunitario de CASA Latina (Historia)], 1950-1999 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Community Relations of CASA Latina (History) [Relaciones Comunitarias de CASA Latina (Historia)], 2001-2004 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - CASA Latina Advisory Council Meeting [Junta del Consejo CASA Latina], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Millionaire Club Meetings of CASA Latina (History) [Reuniones de Club Millonario de CASA Latina (Historia)], 2002 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Note Cards of CASA Latina (History) [Tarjetas de Nota de CASA Latina (Historia) ] (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Case Statement of CASA Latina [El Caso de CASA Latina], 1998-2000 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Participatory Research [Investigación Participativa], 1989 (Box-folder 7/48)
    - History, Tenant Issues & Misc [Historia, Problemas de Inquilinos & Misc], 1998-2006 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - History [Historia], 1998-2000 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - History [Historia] (Box-folder 8/60)
  - Organizational Process and Charts [Subserie B: Organigramas y Proceso de Organización], 2000-2009; Subseries B (Box-folder 1/91, 3/10, 3/78, 4/21, 7/13)
    - Program Sheet of CASA Latina [Hoja de Programa de CASA Latina], 2000 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Institute of Poplar Education of Southern California Organizational Chart [Organigrama del Instituto de Educación Popular del sur de California], 2001 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - CASA Latina Online Hiring Project [CASA Latina Proyecto de Contratación en Línea], 2004 (Box-folder 1/91)
    - Board/Staff Return Planning [Plan de Regreso para Junta Directiva/Personal], 2008 May 2 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - CASA Latina Organigrama [Organizational Chart CASA Latina], 2009 (Box-folder 3/78)
  - Bylaws [Subserie C: Estatutos], 1995-2006; Subseries C (Box-folder 3/7, 4/43)
    - Bylaws/History of CASA Latina [Estatutos/Historia de CASA Latina], 1995-1999 (Box-folder 4/43)
    - Bylaws of CASA Latina [Estatutos de CASA Latina], 2006 (Box-folder 3/77)
  - Employee Handbooks and Training [Subserie D: Manuales y Entrenamiento para Empleos], 2001-2008; Subseries D (Box-folder 1/13, 2/33, 9/19, 9/48, 10/15-20, 11/39)
    - Employee Handbook [Manual para Empleado], 2002-2003 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Crossroads Ministry Anti-Racism Training--Part 1 of 2 [Entrenamiento Anti-Racista Crossroads Ministry--Parte 1 de 2] (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Crossroads Ministry Anti-Racism Training--Part 2 of 2 [Entrenamiento Anti-Racista Crossroads Ministry--Parte 2 de 2] (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Identifying Institutional Racism [Identificando el Racismo Institucional] (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Undoing Institutional Racism [Deshaciendo el Racismo Institucional] (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Race Relations [Relaciones Raciales] (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Participatory Planning--Staff Training [Planificación Participativo--Entrenamiento del Personal] (Box-folder 9/48)
    - StoneSoup (Staff Training) [StoneSoup (Entrenamiento de Personal)], 2001-2004 (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Undoing Racism Training [Entrenamiento de Deshacer Racismo], 2002 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Center for Applied Linguistics (CAL) Training [Entrenamiento del Centro de Lingüística Aplicada (CAL)], 2007 (Box-folder 11/39)
    - Staff Reflection/Training [Entrenamiento y Reflexión de Personal], 2007-2008 (Box-folder 9/19)
- EXECUTIVE BOARD [SERIE 2: JUNTA DIRECTIVA], 1996-2015; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 1/67, 3/1-2, 3/4, 3/6-9, 3/12-76, 3/83-115, 4/6-13, 4/47, 4/49-50, 4/59-68, 4/70-72, 4/78, 7/5-7/7, 9/26, 9/37, 9/56, 10/5, 11/42-45, 13/4-6, Reading Room Virtual Vault)
  Physical and electronic board materials, including historical composition of the board and changes to that structure which took place in 2002, along with related recruitment efforts, orientation materials, meeting minutes, and executive director reports to the board. [Materiales físicos y electrónicos de la junta directiva incluyendo la historia y composición de la junta y cambios a la estructura en el año 2002, esfuerzos de reclutar miembros, materiales de orientación, notas y documentos de juntas y reportes del director ejecutivo a la junta.] directiva]
  - Board History and Composition [Subserie A: Materiales de Orientación y Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva], 1997-2005; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/67, 3/1-2, 3/4, 3/6-9, 3/41, 3/53, 3/65, 4/6, 4/11-12)
    - Committee Reports of Board Recruitment [Informes del Comité de Reclutamiento de la Junta Directiva], 1997 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Committee Reports of Board Recruitment [Informes del Comité de Reclutamiento de la Junta Directiva], 1998 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Committee Reports of Board Recruitment [Informes del Comité de Reclutamiento de la Junta Directiva], 1999 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Pre Work of CASA Latina Board [Trabajo Previo de CASA Latina], 2002 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Orientation For Nuevos Miembros [Orientación de New Members], 2002 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - CASA Latina Leadership History and Composition Process [Historia de Liderazgo y Proceso de Composición de CASA Latina], 2002 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - CASA Latina Board Vision and Composition Process (1 of 2) [Visión y Proceso de Composición de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina (1 de 2)], 2002 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - CASA Latina Board Vision and Composition Process (2 of 2) [Visión y Proceso de Composición de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina (2 de 2)], 2002 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - CASA Latina Board Vision and Composition Process [Visión y Proceso de Composición de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2002 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Responsibilities of Nonprofit Boards [Responsabilidades de Juntas Directivas de Organizaciones sin Fines de Lucro], 2002 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - CASA Latina of board of Directors [CASA Latina Junta Directiva], 2004-2005 (Box-folder 1/67)
    - CASA Board of Directors Contact Information [Información del Contacto de Miembros de Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 October 13 (Box-folder 3/41)
    - CASA Latina Board of Director Contact Information [Información de Contacto de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 (Box-folder 3/53)
    - CASA Latina Board of Director Contact Information [Información de Contacto de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2009 (Box-folder 3/65)
  - Board Training and Orientation Materials [Subserie B: Materiales de Orientación y Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva], 1996-2003; Subseries B (Box-folder 3/12, 3/16, 4/7-8, 4/10, 4/47,4/49-50, 4/78, 10/5)
    - Para Evitar Problemas Legales Cada Miembrx dela Junta Directiva Debe [To Avoid Legal Problems, each Board Member Should], 1999 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Para Evitar Problemas Legales Cada Miembrx dela Junta Directiva Debe [To Avoid Legal Problems, each Board Member Should], 2003 March (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Board of Directors Training (1 of 2) [Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva (1 de 2)], 1998 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Board of Directors Training (2 of 2) [Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva (2 de 2)], 1998 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - CASA Latina Board Training (1 of 3) [Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina (1 de 3)], 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4/47)
    - CASA Latina Board Training (2 of 3) [Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva CASA Latina (2 de 3)], 1996-1999 (Box-folder 4/78)
    - CASA Latina Board Training (3 of 3) [Entrenamiento de la Junta Directiva CASA Latina (3 de 3)], 1997-1998 (Box-folder 4/49)
    - Board Orientation [Orientación de la Junta Directiva], 1998 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - CASA Latina Board Member Manual [Manual para Miembros de la Junta Directive CASA Latina], 1999 (Box-folder 4/50)
    - Board Orientation Handbook [Manual para Orientar la Junta Directiva], 2011 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Meeting Minutes and Attached Materials [Subserie C: Notas y Documentos de la Junta Directiva], 1995-2015; Subseries C (Box-folder 3/13-15, 3/17-76, 3/83-115, 4/9, 4/13, 4/59-68, 4/70-72, 7/5-7/7, 9/26, 9/37, 9/56, 11/42-45, 13/4-6)
    - CASA Latina Board Agenda [Agenda de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 January (Box-folder 3/14)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Agenda [Agenda de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 February (Box-folder 3/15)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 April (Box-folder 3/17)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 May (Box-folder 3/18)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Agenda [Agenda de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 June (Box-folder 3/19)
    - CASA Latina Executive Committee Special Meeting Minutes [Actas de la Junta Especial del Comité Ejecutivo de CASA Latina], 2003 July (Box-folder 3/20)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Agenda [Agenda de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 September (Box-folder 3/21)
    - CASA Latina Board Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 October (Box-folder 3/22)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Agenda [Agenda de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 November (Box-folder 3/23)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2003 December (Box-folder 3/24)
    - CASA Latina Notice of Annual Meeting [Anuncio de la Reunión Anual de CASA Latina], 2004 January 8 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 February 9 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 March 11 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - CASA Latina General Board Meeting [Reunión General de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 April 8 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - CASA Latina Board of Directors Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 May 13 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - CASA Latina General Board Meeting [Reunión General de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 June 10 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - CASA Latina Board Special Meeting [Reunión Especial de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 July 15 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - CASA Latina General Board Meeting [Reunión General de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 September 9 (Box-folder 3/33)
    - CASA Latina General Board Meeting [Reunión General de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 October 14 (Box-folder 3/34)
    - CASA Latina General Board Meeting [Reunión General de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 November 11 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - CASA Latina General Board Meeting [Reunión General de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2004 December 9 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 October (Box-folder 3/43)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 April (Box-folder 3/44)
    - CASA Latina Board of Directors' Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 May (Box-folder 3/45)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 June (Box-folder 3/46)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 July (Box-folder 3/47)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 September (Box-folder 3/48)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 October (Box-folder 3/49)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 November (Box-folder 3/50)
    - CASA Latina Board of Directors Minutes [Actas de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 December (Box-folder 3/51)
    - CASA Latina Board Annual Meeting [Reunión Anual de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 January (Box-folder 3/54)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 March (Box-folder 3/55)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 April (Box-folder 3/56)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 May (Box-folder 3/57)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 June (Box-folder 3/58)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2005 July (Box-folder 3/59)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting via Telephone Conference Call [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de Casa Latina por Conferencia Telefónica], 2008 August (Box-folder 3/60)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 September (Box-folder 3/61)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 October (Box-folder 3/62)
    - CASA Latina Board Meeting [Reunión de la Junta Directiva de CASA Latina], 2008 November (Box-folder 3/63)